Wallen, Saul Papers 5012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Trans World Airlines, (TWA), Inc. 1958-67 (Box 150)
  - Trans World Airlines -and- I.A.M., 1965 (Box 150, Folder 13)
  - Trans World Airlines -and- I.A.M., 1965 (Box 150, Folder 14)
  - Trans World Airlines -and- I.A.M., 1965 (Box 150, Folder 15)
  - Trans World Airlines -and- I.A.M. Grievance 18303, 1965 (Box 150, Folder 16)
- Trans World Airlines, (TWA), Inc. 1958-67 (Box 151)
  - Trans World Airlines -and- ALSSA Lamer Case 64-24, 1966 (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Trans World Airlines -and- I.A.M., 1966 (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - Trans World Airlines -and- I.A.M. Mila Operation Gr. 1375, 1965 (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - Trans World Airlines -and- I.A.M. Dist. 142 Grievance 1379, 1965 (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - Trans World Airlines -and- I.A.M. Lodge 142 Grievance 13200-18528, 1966 (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - Trans World Airlines -and- I.A.M. Grievance 15332 - MCI, 1966 (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - Trans World Airlines -and- I.A.M. Dist. 142 Gr. Hart Disch, 1966 (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - Trans World Airlines -and- I.A.M., 1965 (Box 151, Folder 8)
  - Trans World Airlines -and- I.A.M. Dist. 142 Grievance 260, 1966 (Box 151, Folder 9)
  - Trans World Airlines -and- I.A.M. dist. 142 Grievance 2375, 1967 (Box 151, Folder 10)
  - Trans World Airlines -and- I.A.M. Dist. 142 Grievance e 100144, 1967 (Box 151, Folder 11)
  - Trans World Airlines -and- ALSSA HP 65-28, 1967 (Box 151, Folder 12)
  - Trans World Airlines -and- I.A.M. District 142, 1967 (Box 151, Folder 13)
  - Trans World Airlines, 1967 (Box 151, Folder 14)
- Trans World Airlines, 2/5/68; Union Street Railway Co., 4/10/50 (Box 152)
  - Trans World Airlines, Inc. -and- I.A.M., 1968 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Trans World Airlines -and- A.L.P.A. Case 6625, 1968 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - Trawler Medford, Inc., 1945 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Trawler Medford Inc., 1945 (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - Trawler "Winchester", 1945 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Trawler "Brookline", 1945 (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - "The Cormorant" of General Seafoods Corp., 1945 (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - Triangle Publications Inc. -and- Television Broadcasting Studio Employees, Local 804 I.A.T.S.E., 1960 (Box 152, Folder 8)
  - Tubular Rivet and Stud Co. and I.A.M., Granite Lodge 1451, 1952 (Box 152, Folder 9)
  - Tubular Rivet and Stud Co. Wollaston, Mass. -and Lodge 1451 I.A.M., 1957 (Box 152, Folder 10)
  - Twitchell-Champlin company and Truck Drivers, Warehousemen and Helpers Union, 1947 (Box 152, Folder 11)
  - Tyer Rubber Company -and- URCLPWA - Local 137, 1952 (Box 152, Folder 12)
  - Underwood Corporation Bridgeport, Connecticut -and- IUE - CIO Local 267 H-L-10-55 L-14347, 1956 (Box 152, Folder 13)
  - Underwood Corporation -and- IUE-CIO, Local 267, 1956 (Box 152, Folder 14)
  - Union Carbide Corp. -mad- I.B.T. Local 443, 1965 (Box 152, Folder 15)
  - Union Carbide Corp. -and- IBTCWH Local 25, 1965 (Box 152, Folder 16)
  - Union Carbide Corp. -and- Teamsters, Chauffeurs Local 443, 1965 (Box 152, Folder 17)
  - Union Carbide Corp. -and- Teamsters, Local 478 67A/5375, 1967 (Box 152, Folder 18)
  - Union Hardware Company and Un. Of Electrical Workers Local 247, 1952 (Box 152, Folder 19)
  - Union Hardware Co. and International Union of Electrical Workers CIO, 1953 (Box 152, Folder 20)
  - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Works, CIO, Local 247 and Union Hardware Company, 1954 (Box 152, Folder 21)
  - Union Hardware Company Torrington, Connecticut -and- I.U.E. - Local 247, 1957 (Box 152, Folder 22)
  - Union Leader Corp. Manchester N.H. -and- Newspaper Guild of Manchester, N.H. Case L-32339 Bos. L-166-61, 1961 (Box 152, Folder 23)
  - Union Leader Corp. of New Hampshire -and- International Printing Pressmen and Assistants of No. Am. Local 267, 1962 (Box 152, Folder 24)
  - Union Manufacturing Co. -and- United Electrical Workers, 1957 (Box 152, Folder 25)
  - Union News Company New York, N.Y. -and- N.E. Joint Bf. Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, 1958 (Box 152, Folder 26)
  - U.S. Plywood Corporation -and- Local 25 International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1955 (Box 152, Folder 27)
  - Union Street Railway Company -and- Amal. Assoc. of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employee -Division 1037, 1950 (Box 152, Folder 28)
- Union Twist Drill Co., 11/17/54; United States Steel Corp., 12/13/61 (Box 153)
  - Union Twist Drill Co. -and- United Steelworkers of Am. CIO, 1954 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - Union Twist Drill Co. -and- United Steelworkers of Am. CIO Local 2807, 1954 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Union Twist Drill Co. -and- United Steelworkers of Am. Local 2807, 1955 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Union Twist Drill Co. -and- United Steelworkers of Am. Local 2807, 1955 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Union Twist Drill Co. -and- United Steelworkers of Am. CIO, 1956 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Union Twist Drill Co. -and- United Steelworkers of Am., 1955 (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - S.W. Card Division Union Twist Drill Co. -and- Snyper and Tepper City, 1958 (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - United Air Lines Case UAL-FEIA System Board, 1957 (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - United Air Lines, Inc. Chicago, Ill. -and- International Assn. of Machinists. Grievance 23803-8 SFO, 1958 (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - United Air Lines -and- System Board of Adjustment Griev. 24648 Den, 1960 (Box 153, Folder 10)
  - United Air Lines, and Air Line Pilots, 1962 (Box 153, Folder 11)
  - United Air Lines Air Lines Pilots Assn. Steward and Stewardess Div. System Board of Adjustment, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 12)
  - United Air Lines, Inc. Chicago, Ill. -and- ALP Assn. Stewards and Stewardesses', 1962 (Box 153, Folder 13)
  - United Air Lines, Chicago, Illinois -and- Air Lines Pilots' Assn. International, 1962 (Box 153, Folder 14)
  - United Air Lines System Board of Adjustment Steward and Stewardesses Division Air Line Pilots Assn. Case 63-1, 1963 (Box 153, Folder 15)
  - United Air Lines and A.L.P.A. 63-20 63-21, 1964 (Box 153, Folder 16)
  - United Farmers of N.E. -and- Milk Wagon Drivers and Creamery Workers Union Local 380, 1959 (Box 153, Folder 17)
  - United Illuminating Co. Federation of Utility Employees, 1967 (Box 153, Folder 18)
  - American Newspaper Guild (United Press Assn.), 1955 (Box 153, Folder 19)
  - United Press International -and- Commercial Telegraphers Union, 1960 (Box 153, Folder 20)
  - United Press International -and- Commercial Telegraphers' Union Advisory Arbitration, 1960 (Box 153, Folder 21)
  - United Press International -and- Com'l. Telegraphers' Union, 1964 (Box 153, Folder 22)
  - United Printers and Publishers, Inc. Rust Craft Park, Dedham, Mass. -and- Local 264 International Assoc. of Machinists, 1962 (Box 153, Folder 23)
  - U.S. Envelope Company -and- Federal Labor Union Bos.-L-259-65 L-47910, 1966 (Box 153, Folder 24)
  - U.S. Plywood, 1955 (Box 153, Folder 25)
  - United States Rubber Company Naugatuck, Connecticut, 1946 (Box 153, Folder 26)
  - United States Rubber Company -and- Marine and Shipbuilding Workers Union, 1948 (Box 153, Folder 27)
  - United States Steel Supply Company -and- United Steelworkers of America-CIO, 1949 (Box 153, Folder 28)
  - United States Steel Supply Company -and- United Steelworkers of America-CIO, 1949 (Box 153, Folder 29)
  - Board of Arbitration U.S. Steel Corporation -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1961 (Box 153, Folder 30)
  - United States Steel Corp. -and- United Steelworkers of Am. Case No. USC-1161, 1961 (Box 153, Folder 31)
  - United States Steel Corp. -and- United Steelworkers of Am. Case No. USC-1175, 1961 (Box 153, Folder 32)
  - United States Steel Corp. -and- United Steelworkers of Am. Case No. USC-1148, USC-1161, 1961 (Box 153, Folder 33)
  - United States Steel Corp. -and- United Steelworkers of Am. Case No. USC-1179 Griev. A-60-206, 1961 (Box 153, Folder 34)
- United States Steel Corp. 6/22/62 - Victory Tanning Co., 11/13/56 (Box 154)
  - United States Steel Co. Gary Sheet and Tin Docket USE 1418 Griev. No. S-61-9, 1962 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - United States Steel Corp. -and- United Steelworkers of Am. Case No. USC-1322-1331 Grievance A-61-104, A-61-105, 1962 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - United States Steel Co. Gary Sheet and Tin Docket USC-1420 Griev. S-61-13, 14, 1962 (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - United States Steel USC-1419 S-61-12, 1962 (Box 154, Folder 4)
  - United States Steel Docket USC 1317 Grievance A-61-9, 1962 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - United States Steel Docket No. USA - 1335 Fairless Works Gr. A-61-128 and 9, 1962 (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - United States Steel Fairless Works and US of Am. Loc. 4889 A61-195 61-227, 1962 (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - United States Steel Fairless Works and US of Am. Docket 1313 Griev. A-61-61, 1962 (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - United States Steel Fairless Works and US of Am. Docket USC-1245 Griev A-61-118, 1962 (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - United States Steel Office and Clerical Employees American Bridge Div. Elmira Plant Griev. S-60-2, 3, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 1962 (Box 154, Folder 10)
  - United States Steel Docket USC 1333 Grievance A-61-116, 1962 (Box 154, Folder 11)
  - United States Steel Corp. -and- U.S.W.A. U.S.C. 1335, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 12)
  - United States Steel Corp. Board of Arbitration, (and) United Steelworkers of America, Pittsburgh, Pa., 1963 (Box 154, Folder 13)
  - United States Steel Corp. Fairless Works and US of Am. Local 4889 160a-9, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 14)
  - United Waste Company United Textile Workers of America, 1959 (Box 154, Folder 15)
  - Universal Shoe, 1962 (Box 154, Folder 16)
  - Universal Tanning Company -and- I.F.L.W.U. -CIO, 1949 (Box 154, Folder 17)
  - Universal Tanning Company -and- I.F.L.W.U. Local 21, 1950 (Box 154, Folder 18)
  - Universal Tanning Company -and- I.F.L.W.U. Local 21, 1950 (Box 154, Folder 19)
  - Universal Tanning Company -and- I.F.L.W.U. Local 21, 1951 (Box 154, Folder 20)
  - Universal Tanning Company -and- I.F.L.W.U. Local 21, 1951 (Box 154, Folder 21)
  - Universal Tanning Co. -and- I.F.L.W.U., Local 21, 1953 (Box 154, Folder 22)
  - Universal Tanning Co. -and- I.F.L.W.U., Local 21, 1953 (Box 154, Folder 23)
  - Universal Tanning Co. -and- I.F.L.W.U. Local 21, 1954 (Box 154, Folder 24)
  - Universal Tanning Company -and- I.F.L.W.U. Local 21, 1954 (Box 154, Folder 25)
  - Universal Tanning co. -and- I.F.L.W.U. Local 21, 1954 (Box 154, Folder 26)
  - Universal Tanning Co. -and- I.F.L.W.U., Local 21, 1955 (Box 154, Folder 27)
  - Universal Tanning Co. -and- Local 21, Leathers Workers Union, 1955 (Box 154, Folder 28)
  - Universal Tanning Co. Lynnfield, Mass. -and- Leather Workers International Union Local 21, 1956 (Box 154, Folder 29)
  - Universal Winding Company Providence R.I. -and- International Association of Machinist Lodge 1605, 1955 (Box 154, Folder 30)
  - Universal Winding Company -and- International Assoc. of Mach., Lodge 1605, 1955 (Box 154, Folder 31)
  - Utica Drop Forge and Tool Utica, New York -and- International Association of Machinists Local 1509, 1961 (Box 154, Folder 32)
  - Universal Tanning Co. -and- Leather Workers International Union Local 21, 1956 (Box 154, Folder 33)
  - Universal Leather Company -and- I.F.L.W.U. Local 21, 1950 (Box 154, Folder 34)
  - Brotherhood of Shoe and Allied Craftsmen' (Vampers and Stitchers' Locals), 1965 (Box 154, Folder 35)
  - Vampers, 1953 (Box 154, Folder 36)
  - Vermont Structural Steel Corp. -and- United Steelworkers of America AFL-CIO, 1958 (Box 154, Folder 37)
  - Vermont Structural Steel Corp. -and- U.S.W.A. Dist. 1, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 38)
  - Vermont Tap + Die, 1965 (Box 154, Folder 39)
  - Verza Tanning Co. -and- I.F.L.W.U. Local 21, 1948 (Box 154, Folder 40)
  - Verza Tanning Company -and- I.F.L.W.U. Local 21, 1950 (Box 154, Folder 41)
  - Verza Tanning Company -and- I.F.L.W.U. -CIO, 1950 (Box 154, Folder 42)
  - Verza Tanning Company -and- I.F.L.W.U. Local 21, 1951 (Box 154, Folder 43)
  - Verza Tanning Company -and- I.F.L.W.U. Local 21, 1951 (Box 154, Folder 44)
  - Verza Tanning Co. -and- I.F.L.W.U., Local 21, 1952 (Box 154, Folder 45)
  - Verza Tanning co. -and- I.F.L.W.U., Local 21, 1952 (Box 154, Folder 46)
  - Verza Tanning Co. -and- I.F.L.W.U., Local 21, 1953 (Box 154, Folder 47)
  - Verza Tanning Co. -and- I.F.L.W.U., Local 21, 1953 (Box 154, Folder 48)
  - Verza Tanning Company -and- I.F.L.W.U. Local 21, 1954 (Box 154, Folder 49)
  - Verza Tanning Company -and- I.F.L.W.U., Local 21, 1955 (Box 154, Folder 50)
  - Verza Tanning Company Leather Workers International Union, 1957 (Box 154, Folder 51)
  - Verza Tanning Co. -and- Leather Workers International Union Local 21, 1963 (Box 154, Folder 52)
  - Verza Tanning Co. -and- L.W.I.U., 1964 (Box 154, Folder 53)
  - Verza Tanning -and- L.W.I.U., Local 21, 1965 (Box 154, Folder 54)
  - Vickers, Inc. -and- I.A.M. Lodge 1335, 1960 (Box 154, Folder 55)
  - Vickers, Inc. -and- I.U.E. Lodge 1335, 1965 (Box 154, Folder 56)
  - Victory Tanning Corp. -and- I.F.L.W.U. Local 21, 1948 (Box 154, Folder 57)
  - Victory Tanning Co. Leather Workers International Union of Am., 1956 (Box 154, Folder 58)
- Wakefield Fellmongers Co. 11/20/51 - Warner Gear Div., Borg-Warner Corp., 6/8/66 (Box 155)
  - Wakefield Fellmongers Company -and- I.F.L.W.U. Local 21, 1951 (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - The Wallingford Steel Co. United Steelworkers of America, 1958 (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - Wallingford Steel Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America, Local 2242, 1959 (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - The Wallingford Steel Company -and- United Steelworkers of America, Local 2242, 1959 (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - Wallingford Steel Company -and- United Steelworkers of America, Local 2242, 1959 (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - Wallingford Steel Company -and- United Steelworkers of America, Local 2242, 1959 (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - Wallingford Steel Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1961 (Box 155, Folder 7)
  - Waltham Precision Instrument Co. Inc. -and- Waltham Watch Workers Union, 1963 (Box 155, Folder 8)
  - Waltham Screw Co. -and- UAW AFL CIO Case L-29923 Bos. L-23-61, 1961 (Box 155, Folder 9)
  - Waltham Street Company UAW - Local 209 Griev. A-70956-57 Case L-22923 Bos. L-23-61, 1961 (Box 155, Folder 10)
  - Waltham Watch Company -and- Waltham Watch Workers Union, 1955 (Box 155, Folder 11)
  - The Walton Lunch Company -and- International Bro. of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen Teamsters Local 646, 1949 (Box 155, Folder 12)
  - The Walworth Company -and- United Steelworkers, Local 2394, 1946 (Box 155, Folder 13)
  - The Walworth Company -and- United Steelworkers of America, Local 2394, 1947 (Box 155, Folder 14)
  - Walworth Company (Boston Works) -and- United Steelworkers (Local 2394), 1955 (Box 155, Folder 15)
  - Walworth Company -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1956 (Box 155, Folder 16)
  - Walworth Company -and- United Steelworkers of America, Local 2394, 1956 (Box 155, Folder 17)
  - Walworth Company -and- U.S.W.A., 1963 (Box 155, Folder 18)
  - Walworth Company -and- U.S.W.A. Local 2394, 1964 (Box 155, Folder 19)
  - Walworth Company -and- U.S.W.A. Local 2394, 1967 (Box 155, Folder 20)
  - Walworth Company -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1967 (Box 155, Folder 21)
  - Warner Gear Div. Muncie, Indiana -and- U.A.W. Local 287, 1964 (Box 155, Folder 22)
  - Warner Gear Corp. Muncie, Indiana and U.A.W. Local 287, 1965 (Box 155, Folder 23)
  - Warner Gear Corp. Muncie, Indiana -and- U.A.W. Local 287 1316, 1965 (Box 155, Folder 24)
  - Warner Gear Corp. Muncie, Indiana -and- U.A.W. Local 287 2155, 1965 (Box 155, Folder 25)
  - Warner Gear Corp. Muncie, Indiana -and- U.A.W. Local 287 692, 1965 (Box 155, Folder 26)
  - Warner Gear Corp. Muncie, Indiana -and- U.A.W. Local 287 1955, 1965 (Box 155, Folder 27)
  - Warner Gear Corp. Muncie, Indiana -and- U.A.W. Local 287, 1964 (Box 155, Folder 28)
  - Warner Gear Corp. Muncie, Indiana -and- U.A.W. Local 287 Gr. 2060, 1965 (Box 155, Folder 29)
  - Warner Gear Corp Borg-Warner Corp. -and- U.A.W. Local 287 Gr. 771, 1965 (Box 155, Folder 30)
  - Warner Gear Corp. Borg-Warner Corp. -and- U.A.W. Local 287 Gr. 2514, 1965 (Box 155, Folder 31)
  - Warner Gear Corp. Borg-Warner Corp. -and- U.A.W. Local 287 Gr. 2585, 1965 (Box 155, Folder 32)
  - Warner Gear Corp. Muncie, Indiana -and- U.A.W. Local 287 Gr. 772, 1966 (Box 155, Folder 33)
  - Warner Gear Corp. -and- U.A.W. Local 287 Griev. 2067, 1966 (Box 155, Folder 34)
  - Warner Gear Corp. Muncie, Indiana -and- U.A.W. Local 287 Griev. 221, 1966 (Box 155, Folder 35)
  - Warner Gear Corp. Borg-Warner Corp. -and- U.A.W. Local 287 Griev. 2555, 1966 (Box 155, Folder 36)
  - Warner Gear Division Borg-Warner Corp. -and- U.A.W. Local 287 Griev. 2687, 1966 (Box 155, Folder 37)
  - Warner Gear Division Borg-Warner Corp. -and- U.A.W. Local 287 Griev. 2682, 1966 (Box 155, Folder 38)
- Warner Gear Division Borg-Warner Corp. -and- U.A.W. Local 287 Gr. 225, 1966 (Box 156, Folder 1)
- Warner Gear Division Borg-Warner Corp. -and- U.A.W. Local 287 2679, 2681, 2684, 1966 (Box 156, Folder 2)
- Warner Gear Division Borg-Warner Corp. -and- U.A.W. Local 287 Griev. 1962, 1966 (Box 156, Folder 3)
- Warner Gear Division Borg-Warner Corp. -and- U.A.W. Local 287 Griev. 2080, 1966 (Box 156, Folder 4)
- Warner Gear Div. Borg-Warner Corp. -and- U.A.W. Local 287 Griev. 1363, 1966 (Box 156, Folder 5)
- Warner Gear Division Borg-Warner Corp. -and- U.A.W. Local 287 Griev. 760, 1966 (Box 156, Folder 6)
- Warner Gear Division Borg-Warner Corp. -and- U.A.W. Local 287 Gr. 2793, 1967 (Box 156, Folder 7)
- Warner Gear Division Borg-Warner Corp. -and- U.A.W. Local 287 Gr. 2745, 1967 (Box 156, Folder 8)
- Warner Gear Division Borg-Warner Corp. -and- U.A.W. Local 287 Gr. 2733, 1967 (Box 156, Folder 9)
- Warner Gear Division Borg-Warner Corp. -and- U.A.W. Local 287 Gr. 821, 820, 1967 (Box 156, Folder 10)
- Warner Gear Division Borg-Warner Corp. -and- U.A.W. Local 287 Gr. 2634, 1967 (Box 156, Folder 11)
- Warner Gear Division Borg-Warner Corp. -and- U.A.W. Local 287 Gr. 2735, 1967 (Box 156, Folder 12)
- Warner Gear Division Borg-Warner Corp. -and- U.A.W. Local 287 Gr. 2657, 1967 (Box 156, Folder 13)
- Warner Gear Division Borg-Warner Corp. -and- U.A.W. Local 287 Gr. 2538, 1967 (Box 156, Folder 14)
- Warner Gear Division Borg-Warner Corp. -and- U.A.W. Local 287 Gr. 305, 1967 (Box 156, Folder 15)
- Warren Pipe Company Inc. -and- United Steelworkers of America - CIO, 1957 (Box 156, Folder 16)
- Warren Foundry and Pipe Corp. -and- United Steel Workers of America, 1954 (Box 156, Folder 17)
- Warren Foundry and Pipe Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1956 (Box 156, Folder 18)
- Waterbury Companies, Inc. -and- UAW Local 1251 Case No. L-20204 Hart. L-161-57, 1957 (Box 156, Folder 19)
- Waterbury Companies, Inc. -and- UAW - Local 1251 L-21689 Hart. L-68-58, 1959 (Box 156, Folder 20)
- Waterbury Companies, Inc. -and- UAW Local 1251, 1959 (Box 156, Folder 21)
- Waterbury Farrel Foundry and Machine -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 3381, 1951 (Box 156, Folder 22)
- Waterbury-Farrell Div. Textron, Corp. -and- U.S.W.A., 1965 (Box 156, Folder 23)
- Websters Lens Company -and- Local 225 - IUE AFL-CIO, 1959 (Box 156, Folder 24)
- Western Air Lines -and A.L.P.A., 1965 (Box 156, Folder 25)
- Western Air Lines -and A.L.P.A., 1965 (Box 156, Folder 26)
- Western Air Lines -and A.L.P.A. Case 6626, 1966 (Box 156, Folder 27)
- Western Air Lines -and A.L.P.A. Case 5995, 1966 (Box 156, Folder 28)
- Western Air Lines -and A.L.P.A. Case 5932, 1966 (Box 156, Folder 29)
- Western Air Lines -and A.L.P.A. Case 6620, 1966 (Box 156, Folder 30)
- Western Air Lines -and A.L.P.A. Case 5990, 1966 (Box 156, Folder 31)
- Western Air Lines -and A.L.P.A. Case 5997, 1966 (Box 156, Folder 32)
- Western Air Lines -and A.L.P.A. Case 6704, 1966 (Box 156, Folder 33)
- Western Air Lines -and A.L.P.A. Case 6693, 1966 (Box 156, Folder 34)
- Western Air Lines -and A.L.P.A. Case 6694, 1966 (Box 156, Folder 35)
- Western Air Lines -and A.L.P.A. Case 6619, 1966 (Box 156, Folder 36)
- Western Air Lines -and A.L.P.A. Case 6685, 1966 (Box 156, Folder 37)
- Western Air Lines -and A.L.P.A. Case 6816, 1966 (Box 156, Folder 38)
- Western Air Lines -and A.L.P.A. Case 7033, 1966 (Box 156, Folder 39)
- Western Air Lines -and A.L.P.A. Case 7095, 1967 (Box 156, Folder 40)
- Western Air Lines -and A.L.P.A. Case 7398, 1967 (Box 156, Folder 41)
- Western Air Lines -and A.L.P.A. Time Clock Gr., 1967 (Box 156, Folder 42)
- Western Air Lines -and A.L.P.A. Case No. 7526, 1967 (Box 156, Folder 43)
- Western Air Lines -and A.L.P.A. 7180, 1967 (Box 156, Folder 44)
- Western Air Lines -and A.L.P.A. Supplemental, 1967 (Box 156, Folder 45)
- Western Air Lines -and A.L.P.A. Case 7473, 1967 (Box 156, Folder 46)
- Western Air Lines -and A.L.P.A. Case 7598, 1967 (Box 156, Folder 47)
- Western Air Lines -and A.L.P.A., 1967 (Box 156, Folder 48)
- Western Air Lines -and A.L.P.A., 1967 (Box 156, Folder 49)
- Western Air Lines -and A.L.P.A. Case 7826, 1967 (Box 156, Folder 50)
- Western Air Lines -and ALSSA Case 4023, 1968 (Box 156, Folder 51)
- Western Air Lines -and A.L.P.A. Case 7831, 1968 (Box 156, Folder 52)
- Western Air Lines -and A.L.P.A. Case No. 7971, 1968 (Box 156, Folder 53)
- Western Mass. Electric Co., 11/17/54 - Witch City Tanning Co., 12/5/1966 (Box 157)
  - Western Mass. Elec. Co. -and- International Broth. Of Electrical Workers, AFL, 1954 (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Western Mass. Elec. Co. -and- International Broth. Of Electrical Workers, AFL, 1958 (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - The Western Union Telegraph -and- Commercial Telegraphers' Union, 1960 (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - Westinghouse Air Brake Co. -and- United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America - Local 610, 1946 (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - B.F. Sturtevant Company -and- International Association of Machinists, 1949 (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corporation -and- International Union of Electrical Griev. 2018-A, 1958 (Box 157, Folder 6)
  - Westinghouse Electric Corp. -and- International Association of Machinists Case L-33607 Bos. L-7-1962 (Box 157, Folder 7)
  - Westover Fabrics Inc. -and- Textile Workers Union of America CIO, 1946 (Box 157, Folder 8)
  - Wheeler Electric Corp. Waterbury, Connecticut -and- I.B.E.W. AFL-CIO Local 1667 Case L-24713 - Hart. L-75-59, 1959 (Box 157, Folder 9)
  - Whitin Machine Works -and United Steelworkers of America Case L-21999 Bos. L-85-58, 1958 (Box 157, Folder 10)
  - Whiting and Davis Company -and- United Steelworkers of America, CIO, 1951 (Box 157, Folder 11)
  - Whiting Milk Company -and- Wild Wagon Drivers and Creamery Workers Union Local 380, 1950 (Box 157, Folder 12)
  - Whiting Milk Company -and- Milk Wagon and Creamery Workers Union, 1951 (Box 157, Folder 13)
  - Whitney Blake Company -and- United Electric, Radio, and Machine Workers, 1951 (Box 157, Folder 14)
  - Whitney Blake Co. -and- U.E. Local 239 Case L- 25152 Hart. 103-59, 1959 (Box 157, Folder 15)
  - J.O. Whitten Co. -and- I.F.L.W.U. -Local 295, 1949 (Box 157, Folder 16)
  - J.O. Whitten Co. -and- I.F.L.W.U., Local 295, 1954 (Box 157, Folder 17)
  - Whitter-Higgins Col. -and- International Assoc. of Machinists, Lodge 147, 1957 (Box 157, Folder 18)
  - Winslow Bros + Smith, 1949 (Box 157, Folder 19)
  - Winslow Brothers and Smith -and- I.F.L.W.U. Local 26, 1946 (Box 157, Folder 20)
  - Winslow Brothers and Smith -and- I.F.L.W.U. Case 2, 1946 (Box 157, Folder 21)
  - Winslow Brothers and Smith -and- I.F.L.W.U. Case 4, 1947 (Box 157, Folder 22)
  - Winslow Brothers and Smith -and- I.F.L.W.U. Local 26, 1947 (Box 157, Folder 23)
  - Winslow Brothers and Smith -and- I.F.L.W.U. Local 26 Case 6, 1947 (Box 157, Folder 24)
  - Winslow Brothers and Smith -and- I.F.L.W.U. Local 26 Case 7, 1947 (Box 157, Folder 25)
  - Winslow Brothers and Smith -and- I.F.L.W.U. Local 26 Case 8, 1947 (Box 157, Folder 26)
  - Winslow Brothers and Smith -and- I.F.L.W.U. Local 26 Case 9, 1947 (Box 157, Folder 27)
  - Winslow Brothers and Smith -and- I.F.L.W.U. Local 26 Case 10, 1947 (Box 157, Folder 28)